Hi, how are you? My name is Rhys with Roof ER. We're a local roofing company that specializes in helping homeowners get their roof replaced, paid for by their insurance.
We've had a lot of storms here in Virginia over the past few months that have done a lot of damage.
We're already working with your neighbors. We've been able to help them get fully approved through their insurance company to have their roof replaced.
So what I'm here to do today is a completely free inspection to see if you have similar, qualifyable damage.
If you do, I'm going to take a bunch of photos and walk you through the rest of the process of getting you approved for your insurance.
If you don't, I'll let you know that your roof's in good shape and that you'll have the peace of mind that you have no issues.
Okay, great. So it's going to take me about 10 to 15 minutes total.
I'm going to walk around the perimeter of your home, grab my ladder, and then check out your roof.
Do you know your insurance company? State Farm? Great. We work with those guys all the time.
Here's my flyer. Look us up while I'm on the roof. I'm sure you'll be happy with what you find.
I'll give you a knock when I finish up.